you look so adorable absolutely perfect look this way oh my gosh yes you're so good
inou is a great photographer it's obvious she loves it we should do a shot of both of you next
heck yeah i think we should get the shot where shion first turns into black lily
and black lobellia tries to find out whether she's really on her side it'll be amazing
so down what do you think sis is that okay sure i'm all right so far the abandoned hospital is a
little creepy but at least there are enough of us here to be distracting i guess it's manageable
let's just make it quick
wait something's not right here kitakawa what are you doing black lobellia always has a sad face
you're smiling way too much you're so so so cute i'm sorry i bet i totally ruined that shot
it's fine i guess i'm having hella fun you guys i'm so sorry it's like i'm possessed by this stupid
grin on my face i totally get it it feels like you just can't help but smile oh we've got what is
wrong with her she's goofing off and she's totally out of character it's ridiculous and it's cutting
into our shoot time i can't bear to watch this cosplayers like her are the absolute worst
what am i supposed to do with you
let's get some solo shots with you now marine i'm all about it wakana gojo what's up
thanks for doing this you've made shinju very happy oh i didn't do much i know that's not true
i'm sure you only had her pay for the extra material for her outfit right
huh i knew it there are other costs incurred here transportation tools and props for example
i'll pay you back for it i'm sorry she said she just gets an allowance so it's fine no it's not
good artists need to be paid for their work
thank you though for giving her such a great experience today honestly i had no idea she loved
so much so much that she wanted to cosplay him it makes me wonder why she felt like she had to hide
it from me i failed her i guess you didn't do anything wrong inui i promise it's just that it takes a lot
of courage you know telling others about the things you love things you want to try it can be scary
sometimes i know how that feels you took something that's so precious to me and you
you handled it with such care and consideration there's something about you
you're wonderful but did you say something who me not a word
that's the last thing i need you to hear perfect now turn this way slowly
i got the most gorgeous shot of you just now for real yes
what was that noise whoa she and you uh not to make it awkward but your bongos are going bonkers
all i had was the natural light spill in the studio but it ended up working out perfectly
i really love this shot in particular i agree it looks great she nailed the character
the outfit looks perfect on her yeah it's nice she brought more depth than i expected her to
i thought i felt love at first sight with the outfit wakanagoja created
but i guess it was about more than that
did you like my cosplay or was it too weird for you
what no not at all why would you ask that
it's just that i could never pull a cosplay like that off
so i'm in awe guess i got a little jealous too
okay what was that are you possessed or something
my whole world just turned upside down there's a cosplay that you can't pull off
and you're jealous of me what are you talking about i'm human too
yeah sure but you always look amazing in everything
nope that's not true i pick from the characters i like that have the same shape and size as i do that's all
i mean i'd love to cosplay black lobelia or soma too but they're tall characters and it wouldn't look right
i don't want to wear something that isn't perfect
it's not like i have low self-esteem or something
it's just that sometimes i wish i could change my appearance
i feel like i could have done things better
like if i had a more feminine figure like you
i could knock off so many other cosplays on my wish list
and i'm sorry
i really am quite jealous of you
my point was we don't always know how someone really feels
but well we all have struggles
here's the plan
when i'm in high school i'll get a job to save money
and then we can do it
cosplay together
are you kidding me
yes please
do you mean that really
uh-huh
i spent way too much money this time
so it might take a minute to save up again
but once i do
i'm gonna take a break from group cosplay
i definitely learned that i prefer doing photo shoots with just you
today was so exhausting
yeah it was a lot
but i had so much fun
oh
i'm glad we did this group shoot
uh yeah
me too
i mean i guess it wasn't the worst thing
maybe someday
i might like to try it again
hey
oh my gosh gojo
did shinju send you the files yet
i'm dying over here
they're amazing
i'm looking at them right now
i know right
i'm so freaking hyped about them
that i'm watching blaze again
for the 800th time
but back to the important stuff
gojo was that your first time doing dude makeup
you are a god
i just read a magazine on how to do cosplay makeup
yeah i read them too and i can't do what you did
juju was super cute as per usual
but shinji was so hot i almost died
it was the best
and i totes called it on shinji wanting to cosplay
it was awesome seeing her let loose
and it seemed like she had fun
yeah it did
lots of fun
that's totally your uniform isn't it
it is
when she told me how she felt
i couldn't help but relate
so yeah
that's why i wanted to help her
wait are you saying you want to cosplay too
you've got some splaining to do
i'm hurt bro
like i'd ever make fun of your sweet gojo dreams
thanks but that's not what i meant
also i had no idea that you were even building that soma cosplay you little ninja
when did you plan that
not long ago actually
it was right after we went to see the studio
she came over and we started planning that night
that's not true neon
you can't give up now
the three of you have been best friends forever
that's what i thought too
but i was wrong
it's done
after seeing the way those two look at each other
just you two
yes
and she was so embarrassed
she asked me not to tell anyone
honestly
oh
okay
i get it now
it all makes sense
sure it does
are you still there
kitagawa
something wrong
no
why do you ask
why would anything be wrong
i could be wrong
i want to love you
please
you
any
there
you
no
We'll be right back.
Uh-huh.
Her sweet tan, those shark teeth, her look of repulsion, her face is genius, and her underboob. No one can hate on a tasteful underboob. In fact, looking at underboob is good for you. It gives you like dopamine and stuff.
What is she talking about?
Well, yeah. I can make this one pretty quickly.
Are you for real? That's amazing!
Some of the details might be tough, though. Should we retouch them digitally?
That's a great idea!
I finished that one in record time. Maybe because there's not much to it.
Shizuku-tan, Black Lily, and Black Lobelia. It's amazing to think that there are so many unique designs in the world. If I hadn't started making cosplays, I would have never gotten to see them.
Gojo! Are you home?
It's totally foundation, but you can put it on your whole body.
I've never heard of that before.
It's a thing. Hey, I know this is weird, but can I take a swim in your shower? I'm sweating so much and the soup stank is real.
Sure.
Thanks, man! You're a saint.
It's so hot.
Ew, this is disgusting. I really need to be careful or I'm gonna get heat stroke in here and die naked.
I heard you can even get it inside if it's majorly hot out. Crazy stuff.
Kitagawa?
Huh?
Did you bring a change of clothes? If not, you can use some of mine. I'll leave them by the door, okay?
Shut up! Are you sure? Wait a minute. Is this your sneaky way of checking me out in the buff?
I would never do that!
Oh, my bad. But if this were a manga, you totally would, and I'd be all,
Yeah! Gojo, you're such a perv!
I don't want to talk about this!
I'm just messing with you, Dorcas!
Yeah!
Thanks for the shower. I feel brand new.
Sure.
I know I'm the one who let her borrow it, but it's still strange to think about.
She's wearing my P.E. uniform, the same one that touched my body.
And she also used my soap in there, all over her body, which means she smells like me.
What? What is this feeling happening inside me?
Gojo, you're red. What's wrong?
No, I'm not. You're seeing things.
Okay, whatever. I brought these so you can look at them.
This is the foundation I used earlier. And check out this white mascara!
Now I can even have Veronica's eyelashes!
Good find. These are great. Sorry you're the one who has to buy this stuff.
Don't be silly. Emptying my wallet is how I can help support the cause, remember?
Check these out! Only 800 yen in the Halloween section.
I feel like a bandit, for real!
They're also way lighter than they look. It's wild.
I'm gonna go ahead and slip these on.
Okay. What is that?
Oh, this? It looks cool, doesn't it?
It's basically like a giant decal for the wall.
Just roll it on like so.
Ta-da!
Oh!
Looks like a prison now, huh?
That was awesome!
I mean, yeah. It does change things up quite a bit.
And they had all sorts of designs.
We can totes do anything!
I tried to find the teeth, but all I found were some cheesy wolf fangs.
We might have to add them in post, as they say.
I actually have some for you.
Gojo, are we in a horror movie right now?
What? No.
I found out you can make these from fake nails at the 100 yen store, so I tested it out.
Seriously? Can I try them on?
Go ahead.
How do they feel?
They're in!
Here they are! Look good?
They look amazing, Kitakawa!
And they're so much more realistic than I thought they would be!
Too chill!
I'm sorry. It's just... I was worried about those.
It's pretty exciting, right?
I so feel that.
Okay, let me get changed.
You need to get this foundation happening first.
Gojo, could you help me get it on my back later?
That part took forever the first time, and I'm not about it.
What was that she said before about underboob and dopamine?
So, I guess...
That must be what's happening to me.
It hurts.
What the heck?
You're bright red again, man!
Are you dying?
Huh?
Oh, no.
No, I'm fine.
What do we do?
What do you mean?
Let's get you some water!
Ah!
Ow, that hurt!
I hit my head really hard!
Are you okay?
What day is it?
How am I supposed to wear a wig over this thing?
Veronica, love!
I guess we'll just have to meet another time.
Why are you so freaked out?
Well, I don't ever come to Shibuya, so...
I just feel out of place.
I promise you're okay.
What are we gonna buy today?
Normal clothes?
Yep.
It's a men's store.
I don't think anything's gonna fit you in here.
We're here for you.
You were worried about not having more clothes, so...
Time for a change!
Come on!
Let's hit it!
I'll be your own personal stylist.
Which style would you say is most you?
Oh, um...
I don't know.
I've never really thought about it.
Also, I'm not exactly sure how to pick out clothes.
Starting from zero, then, huh?
All right.
Let's experiment with some looks.
How about this?
Go ahead and try it on.
Excuse me, sir!
Yes?
Done yet?
No, not yet.
Can I peek?
Um, I'd rather you not...
Oh, she's insanely hot.
Seems pretty cool, too.
Is that doof in there her boyfriend?
No way.
I, uh...
I'm done.
Come and tell me!
You sound so timid.
Maybe he's younger?
That looks amazing on you.
I am gonna die from not laughing.
Let me know if you need anything else, okay?
Okay, thanks.
I'm gonna go grab a few other pieces for you to try on, cool?
Holy crap!
How would a calm person respond?
He looks totally freaking amazing in every single one of these outfits!
But seriously, what the F?
How does this dude look hot in everything he wears?
I can't get rid of any of these!
A guy this hot actually exists!
I mean, I know he does, because he's right in front of me, but...
I can't, I can't, I can't!
I love him!
I love you, Goju!
Moju!
I love your little face to death!
Kitagawa, can I take this off now?
What?
Why, though?
Well, I feel kind of awkward.
It's a really nice shirt, but I'd never actually wear it, you know what I mean?
No, not really.
Okay, then how about a plain Jane t-shirt?
Less intimidating, right?
Maybe.
It's so cute!
I'm gonna go try on the same one.
Wouldn't it be too big for you, though?
Actually, I wear men's clothes any time I want something a little baggy.
I didn't know that was a thing.
I hope he likes it, because then we'll have matching shirts!
I'll have a shirt that matches the boy I love!
How cute would that be?
What?
Matching outfits?
You can't be serious, can you?
That's so silly!
Stop!
Oh my gosh, you're embarrassing me!
Did you try it on yet?
Uh, yeah, I did.
I'm gonna wear it like this.
What about you, Gojo?
Show me.
You likey?
Hi, likey.
I can see your face!
You suck at lying!
That hat would look great on you!
Why are you freaking out?
It's not alive!
I'm getting a bit hungry.
Wanna take a break somewhere and have a snacky snack?
Ramen, maybe?
Ramen's not a snacky snack!
I'm so sorry, and you picked out so many good options for me, too.
It's fine.
If it doesn't feel right, it doesn't feel right.
Oh, by the way, that monster bump on my head's almost gone now.
So when do you want to do the Veronica cosplay?
Um, I think I'm gonna pass this time.
You'll have to do that one yourself, Kitagawa.
Huh?
Why, though?
You know I can't cosplay without you, Gojo.
I mean, like, what are you saying?
Please say something!
Sorry.
I just can't this time.
It's not you, I promise.
But I hadn't really thought about how I would feel when you put on something like that around me.
It's different from the other cosplays.
It's very revealing.
There's less fabric on your chest, okay?
I couldn't look at you.
Wait, that's all!
Why'd you make it sound all serious?
Oh my god, stop it!
You're so bad!
You scared the crap out of me!
Wait, so all this drama was just you getting embarrassed thinking of my underboom?
You were such a giant purr!
Do you really have to say that so loud?
You know, I guess I never really dwelled on it.
But Veronica does show a lot of skin.
Kind of an understatement.
I didn't really notice it when I saw her in the game for some reason.
Tell you what, I promise to be more sensitive when I pick the next character.
Thank you.
But I mean, you did go through all the trouble of making it for me, so maybe I'll wear it at home?
Uh, sure.
Why not?
It's yours.
I can send you a picture of me wearing it.
I just told you I couldn't look at it!
Why would you even go there?
I'm totally kidding!
I wouldn't do that.
Promise.
What?
Okay.
Move this.
All right.
Like you.
But let's do this!
Did you mind if we ever tolerateühren?
Like you.
How can I feel?
And so I know this is an angry man who has in turn around
Like seeming in looking for a piece for us till the football season
It's beenplays time to the football season
It's been demonstration, color, some takes up
Tell us the football season
It that day should be a struggle
Kiendo R signing truly
Thank you.
Next time.